<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document>
  <properties>
    <title>jDTAUS Banking RI DTAUS</title>
    <author email="cs@jdtaus.org">Christian Schulte</author>
  </properties>
  <body>
    <section name="Introduction">
      <p>
        This artifact provides the jDTAUS <code>PhysicalFileFactory</code>
        reference implementation. Starting with version 1.5 support has been
        added for properties to configure behaviour of the implementation when
        using one of the methods of the <code>PhysicalFileFactory</code>
        interface taking a <code>Properties</code> instance. The following
        properties may be specified:
        <ul>
          <li><code>org.jdtaus.banking.dtaus.ri.zka.DefaultPhysicalFileFactory.readAheadCaching</code><blockquote>
              The <code>readAheadCaching</code> property is used to enabled or
              disable the use of a read-ahead caching algorithm. Its expected
              value is of type <code>Boolean</code> and defaults to
              <code>Boolean.TRUE</code>, if using one of the methods of the
              <code>PhysicalFileFactory</code> interface not taking a
              <code>Properties</code> instance.
          </blockquote></li>
          <li><code>org.jdtaus.banking.dtaus.ri.zka.DefaultPhysicalFileFactory.readAheadCacheSize</code><blockquote>
              The <code>readAheadCacheSize</code> property is used to specify
              the size of the read-ahead cache if the read-ahead caching
              algorithm is enabled. Its expected value is of type
              <code>Integer</code>. If not given a default value is used.
          </blockquote></li>
          <li><code>org.jdtaus.banking.dtaus.ri.zka.DefaultPhysicalFileFactory.coalescingCaching</code><blockquote>
              The <code>coalescingCaching</code> property is used to enabled or
              disable the use of a coalescing caching algorithm. Its expected
              value is of type <code>Boolean</code> and defaults to
              <code>Boolean.TRUE</code>, if using one of the methods of the
              <code>PhysicalFileFactory</code> interface not taking a
              <code>Properties</code> instance.
          </blockquote></li>
          <li><code>org.jdtaus.banking.dtaus.ri.zka.DefaultPhysicalFileFactory.coalescingBlockSize</code><blockquote>
              The <code>coalescingBlockSize</code> property is used to specify
              the block size of the coalescing cache if the coalescing caching
              algorithm is enabled. Its expected value is of type
              <code>Integer</code>. If not given a default value is used.
          </blockquote></li>
          <li><code>org.jdtaus.banking.dtaus.ri.zka.DefaultPhysicalFileFactory.spaceCharactersAllowed.<i>Field</i></code><blockquote>
              The <code>spaceCharactersAllowed</code> property is used to
              specify numeric fields for which space characters are to be
              allowed. It is used as a prefix with the hexadecimal field
              constant appended. Its expected value is of type
              <code>Boolean</code>. By default no space characters are allowed
              for any numeric field. To enable support for space characters for
              e.g. field 10 of an A record (A10) a property with name
              <code>org.jdtaus.banking.dtaus.ri.zka.DefaultPhysicalFileFactory.spaceCharactersAllowed.A10</code>
              needs to be specified with a value equal to <code>Boolean.TRUE</code>.
              This will lead to space characters getting converted to zero
              digits if occuring in field A10.
          </blockquote></li>
        </ul>
      </p>
    </section>
  </body>
</document>
